当然我设置为冰岛时间，因为我们共享
And of course I set it to Icelandic time because we share
爱北极光，Gordy.
a love of the aurora borealis, Gordy.
你不知道怎么看时间
And you have no idea how to tell time.
伟大的礼物,爸爸。
Great gift, Dad.
. . . .
Way to think things through.
不知怎么的，你会认为一个男人
Somehow, you'd think that a man
谁能把火箭送入太空，谁就有能力
who can send a rocket into space would be able
. . . .
to manage a halfway decent birthday present.
不。
Nope.
你知道，Gordy，综合考虑，
You know, Gordy, all things considered,
也许我的礼物并没有那么糟糕
maybe my gift isn't so bad after all.
哦。
Aw.
嘿,戈迪。惊喜!
Hey, Gordy. Surprise!
哇!这里有一个礼物，
Wow! Now, there's a gift.
给你，Gordy.
Here you go, Gordy.
生日快乐。
Happy birthday.
哦,美丽的,哈利。
Oh, beautiful, Haley.
哦。
Aw.
早上好
Good morning on what is
一定是风很大的一个。
sure to be a windy one.
我们有强风警报
We have a high wind warning
前往洛杉矶海岸和山谷
for the L.A. County coast and valleys
如果有云的话，上午10点左右一定会有。
with some clouds sure to come in around 10:00 a.m.
尽管强风警报会，呃，失效
And even though the high gust warning will, um, expire
上午到晚些时候，你还是会想要……
mid to late morning, you'll still want to keep...
搜寻一群失踪的徒步旅行者
The search for a group of missing hikers
将于今晨在阿瓜达尔西外重新开始。
is set to resume this morning just outside Agua Dulce.
旅行团两天前出去了
The tour group went out two days ago
在太平洋山脊步道
and on the Pacific Crest Trail
但那天晚上并没有像预期的那样回来。
but didn't come back as expected that night.
搜救人员昨天早上开始搜寻…
Crews started searching yesterday morning...
而且交通已经很堵了
And traffic is already backed up
因为南向101公路发生了事故。
due to an accident on the southbound 101.
现在是7点44分，波和艾夫斯。
It is 7:44 with Bo and Ives.
爆炸。
Bang.
哇。来吧。
Whoa. Come on.
下来,下来。
Down, down.
下来,下来,下来。
Down, down, down.
砰!是的，一个好孩子。
Bang! Yes, a good boy.
向上起来,起来。
Up. Up, up.
好吧,。起来,起来。
Okay, up. Up, up.
这次我们得小心行事。
Got to keep our heads up out the clouds on this one.
我知道。
I know.
现在，我们降落这个…
Now, we land this...
是的。像六枪。
Yeah. Like Six Guns.
我是说，我们真的表演了一场，
I mean, we really put on a show,
你知道他们会让我们回来拍续集的。
well, you know they're gonna bring us back for the sequel.
嗯哼。
Mm-hmm.
好吧，我们肯定不会再卖马了。
Well, we sure as hell ain't got to sell no more horses.
就执行。
So just execute.
我们不会再有麻烦了。毫米。
And we ain't got no more problems. Mm.
你好吗?
You good?
你的妹妹在哪里?
Where your sister?
那是什么呢?
What's that about?
-她应该在这里的。-是的。
- She's supposed to be here. - Yeah.
该死的。
Goddamn it.
我不是让你修好助行器吗。
Thought I told you to fix the damn walker.
你听到了吗?
You hear that?
持久性有机污染物。
Pops.
-来吧，来吧流行音乐。——萤火虫。
- Come on, come on. Pop. - Firefly.
——还有什么?还有什么?——鬼。
- What else? What else? - Ghost.
啊哈。
Uh-huh.
贝多芬。
Beethoven.
嗯,嗯。
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
——海军准将。-是的。
- Commodore. - Yeah.
维吉尔。
Virgil.
你有好处。你有好处。
You good. You good.
你很好,男人。你有好处。
You good, man. You good.
——鬼。——你有好处。你有好处。你有好处。
- Ghost. - You good. You good. You good.
——弹出?——幸运。
- Pops? - Lucky.
——弹出。持久性有机污染物。——海军准将。
- Pops. Pops. - Commodore.
弹出!
Pops!
橙汁。
OJ.
哦。嗨,horsie。
Oh. Hi, horsie.
嘿,嘿,嘿。请不要直视他的眼睛。
Hey, hey, hey. Don't look him in the eyes, please.
好的。
Okay.
准备好开安全会议了吗?
You ready to do the safety meeting?
我需要5个…
Uh, I'm gonna need like five...
我的团队快到了。
Um, my team's almost here.
你的团队不在这里。
Your team's not here.
好的。持有。
Okay. Hold.
抱歉，那个养马的也在跟我说话。
Sorry, I got the horse guy talking to me, too.
——怎么了?副本。-安全会议在…
- What's up? Copy. - Safety meeting at the...
女士们先生们，有请邦尼·克莱顿女士。
Ladies and gentlemen, Ms. Bonnie Clayton on set.
她来了，各位。
Here she is, everybody.
看看这些。
Take a look at all of that.
芬恩，这是OJ，我们的驯马师。
Fynn, this is OJ, our horse trainer.
你们还记得 Flash Point，
You remember these guys from Flash Point.
是的。嗨。
Yeah. Hi.
嗯…
Uh...
你叫OJ?
Your name is OJ?
是的,奥蒂斯初级。
Yeah, Otis Junior.
哦。
Oh.
嗯…
Uh...
在哪里啊…另一个人吗?
Where's the o... the other guy?
-高年级的那个?-伙计，他死了。
- The-the-the senior guy? - Dude, he died.
大约六个月前。
About six months ago.
一堆乱七八糟的东西从飞机上掉下来。
A bunch of random shit fell out of a plane.
看来我们只能让小詹姆斯待在这里了。
So I guess we're stuck with Junior over here.
——没有。-是的。
- No. - Yeah.
好的。
Okay.
他妈的。太好了。
Fuck. Great.
蚂蚁，情况如何?
Uh, Ant, how we looking?
很好，如果我们要卖马屁股的话。
Yeah, good, if we're selling a horse's ass.
这是,呃,
That's, uh,
传奇摄影师鹿角·霍尔斯特……
legendary cinematographer Antlers Holst over here...
我们去转木马吧。
Let's go ahead and spin the horse.
但你说了"等一下"所以…
But you had said "hold," so...
现在我要说的是“旋转”。我们走吧。-
And now I'm saying "spin." Let's go. -
太好了。一边转，我们能化个妆吗?
Great. And while that's spinning, can we get makeup?
请给邦妮·克莱顿小姐化妆。
Get makeup for Ms. Bonnie Clayton, please.
等一等。
Hold on.
你能离后面远点吗?
Can you step away from the back, please?
他们叫我到这里来。
They told me to come here.
好叫,橙汁。告诉你吧
Good call, OJ. Um, tell you what,
我们开个安全会议吧。
let's do a quick safety meeting.
伙计们，这是OJ，我们的驯马师。
Guys, this is OJ, our horse trainer.
把它搬开。
Take it away.
请把音乐关掉。
Kill the music, please.
我叫OJ。嗯…
My name is OJ. Uh...
我想我妹妹马上就要来了。
I think my sister's gonna be here in a minute.
请大声点。后面的人听不见。
Little louder, please. We cannot hear you in the back.
我说我们是动物牧人
I said we are animal wranglers
和海伍德好莱坞马一起。
with Haywood Hollywood Horses.
,嗯…你知道第一个…
And, uh... did you know the very first, uh, assem...
嘿,你!
Hey, yo!
打扰一下。对不起。
Excuse me. Sorry.
对此我很抱歉。我来算一下。
I'm so sorry about that. Let me do that.
对不起,哥哥。
Sorry, brother.
——安全会议。-是的。
- Safety meeting. - Yeah.
你好!你们过得如何?
Hello! How y'all doing?
抱歉迟到了。
Sorry for the tardiness.
我叫翡翠，是OJ，
My name is Emerald, that's OJ,
我们今天是你的动物牧人
and we are your animal wranglers today
和海伍德好莱坞马一起。
with Haywood Hollywood Horses.
你知道吗，第一个
Now, did you know that the very first
按顺序排列的照片
assembly of photographs in sequential order
制作一部电影
to create a motion picture
是一个黑人骑马的两秒钟片段吗?
was a two-second clip of a Black man on a horse?
是的,它是。是的,它是。查一下。
Yes, it was. Yes, it was. Look it up.
我知道你们认识埃德沃德·迈布里奇，
Now, I know you guys know Eadweard Muybridge,
电影的鼻祖
the grandfather of motion pictures
是谁拍下了这段视频，
who took the pictures that created that clip,
但有人知道黑人骑师的名字吗
but does anybody know the name of the Black jockey
那个骑马的?
that rode the horse?
不。
No.
不?我是说，第一个特技演员，
Nope? I mean, the very first stuntman,
动物饲养员和电影明星的双重身份，
animal wrangler and movie star all rolled into one,
而且根本没有关于他的记录。
and there is literally no record of him.
那人是巴哈马的骑师
That man was a Bahamian jockey
名叫阿利斯泰尔·e·海伍德
that went by the name of Alistair E. Haywood.
他是我的曾曾祖父。
And he is my great-great-grandfather.
太好了。-还有一个“曾祖父”。
Great. -There's another "great" grandfather.
这就是为什么在海伍德牧场，
That's why back at the Haywood Ranch,
作为布莱克在好莱坞唯一的驯马师
as the only Black-owned horse trainers in Hollywood,
我们喜欢说，“既然照片可以移动的瞬间”，
we like to say, "Since the moment pictures could move",
我们也参与其中。”
we had skin in the game."
好了，我们来做些安全防范措施
All right, let's get into some, uh, safety precautions
我们在片场的时候，好吗?
while we're on set, shall we?
第一，请不要发出任何噪音，
Number one, please refrain from making any loud noises,
突然移动，关掉你的手机。
sudden movements, and keep your cell phones off.
我们真的很感激。
We'd really appreciate that.
第二，如果你看到任何看起来或感觉不安全的东西，
Two, if you see anything that looks or feels unsafe,
联系我，OJ或者你的副手。
contact me, OJ or your second in chain of command.
第三，让我们好好拍摄!
And three, let's have a great shoot!
我是Emerald Haywood。
Uh, and I'm Emerald Haywood.
我导演、编剧、制作、表演。
I direct, write, produce, act.
我做一点…♬在一旁唱歌。♪
I do a little... ♪ Singing on the side. ♪
呃,摩托车,宝贝。
Uh, motorcycles, baby.
我做的烤奶酪特别好吃
Look, I-I make a mean grilled cheese
如果你在寻找狡猾。
if you're looking for crafty.
就吼我一声。
Just-just holler at me.
好吧，太棒了。
Okay, that was great.
那是……这是很多。
That was... that was a lot.
我们来排练一下。
Uh, let's do a rehearsal.
——是吗?排练吗?-排练，我们应该。
- Yeah? Rehearsal? - Rehearsing, we should.
我们应该做一个。排练。
We should do one. Rehearsing.
我认为……我觉得他需要休息一下。
I think... I think he might need a break.
是的，我们先排练一个，
Yeah, we'll rehearse one first,
然后休息，对吗?
and then break, yeah?
好吧，我准备好了。
Well, I'm ready to do one.
橙汁,她……她已经准备好了。
OJ, she's... she's ready to do one.
告诉马我们准备好了。
Tell the horse we're ready to do one.
视觉特效组，趁我们还有时间，能把球放进来吗?
VFX, can we get the ball in here while we have a sec?
-嗯-视觉特效呃,,橙汁,
- Em. - VFX. Uh, and, OJ,
你可以…你可以下车了。
you can... you can step off.
走出。一步了。
Step out. Step off.
-是的,是的。-请出去。
- Yeah, yeah. - Uh, step out.
新兴市场?
Em?
那匹马叫什么名字?
What's the horse's name?
——呃,幸运。——幸运。
- Uh, Lucky. - Lucky.
——是吗?——视效!
- Is he? - VFX!
是的。新兴市场?
Yeah. Em?
- OJ，我们走吧-你打电话给我?
- Uh, OJ, let's step off. - You calling me?
-嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿。-我在工作。
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey. - I'm trying to work.
我是怎么跟你说的?
What'd I tell you about that, man?
伙计，如果她不能靠近马背，
Hey, man, if she can't get near the back of the horse,
-我们在这里做什么?-嘿，嘿，嘿!-
- what are we doing here? - Hey, hey, hey, hey! -
——哇!-哇，哇，哇，哇
- Whoa! - Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
哇，哇，哇，哇，哇。医生。
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. -Medic.
哇，哇，哇，哇。
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
-你没事吧?——哇,哇。
- Are you okay? - Whoa, whoa.
听着，也许这太快了，是吧?
Look, maybe it's just too soon, huh?
对，不是gig。我没有准备好。
Yeah, it's not the gig. Not ready yet.
对吧?
Right?
-我们需要它，伙计-不，我知道
- We need it, man. - No, I know.
你爸爸留下了一个大洞。我知道。
Your dad left an enormous hole. I know that.
但别担心，会有其他人的。
But don't worry, there'll be others.
好吧?我很抱歉。
All right? I'm sorry.
- - -…——对不起。
- And... - Sorry.
你跟她道歉就行了。
Just, you tell her sorry.
谢谢你给我这个机会。
Thank you for the opportunity.
来吧,现在。
Come on, now.
哦,视效在哪儿?
Oh, where's VFX?
哦,好吧。你明白了。
Oh, all right. You got it.
对不起,这是……
Sorry, that was...
我要把你送到哪里?
So, where am I dropping you?
我和你一起上去。
I'm-a go up with you.
我需要些东西。
I need to get some shit.
我的小女儿说，你知道，我可以在她那里借宿，
My little girl said, you know, I could crash at her place,
所以我明早就走了
so I'll be gone in the morning.
那我明天开车送你回去?
So I'm gonna drive you back tomorrow?
我可以找到车。
I can find a ride.
我是说，我能从这贱人身上喝到橙汁吗?
But, I mean, like, can I get fun OJ out this bitch?
因为这该死的橙汁
'Cause this wack-ass OJ
真的让我觉得我不被爱
is really making me feel like I'm not loved.
你想让你妹妹有这种感觉吗?
Is that how you want your little sister to feel?
淘金热怎么了?
What happened to Gold Rush?
淘金热破产了。
Gold Rush went bankrupt.
这种情况已经持续三年了。
It's been this for three years.
——该死的。——你好,人。
- Damn. - Howdy, folks.
欢迎来到Jupiter’s Claim。
Welcome to Jupiter's Claim.
走到许愿井上去吧。
Step on up for the wishing well.
找你的朱普·詹格尔。
Get your Jupe Jangle.
去吧，在井边照张相。
Go on, take a picture at the well.
牛仔和女牛仔,
Cowboys and cowgirls,
只是提醒你一下。
just a little heads-up.
请于周五下午五点半加入我们的全新节目
Join us Fridays at 5:30 p.m. for the brand-spanking-new
木星的星际套索经验。
Jupiter's Claim Star Lasso Experience.
来圣代酒吧吧。
Come on over to the Sundae Saloon.
拿上冰凉的沙士。
Get your ice-cold sarsaparilla.
看看这个。我从来没见过这样的东西。
Look at this. I've never seen anything like it.
——哦,史……- - - - - -来吧。
- Oh, shi... - Come on.
对不起,你们。我很抱歉。
I'm sorry, y'all. I'm sorry.
——照片炸弹。-你毁了它。
- Photo bomb. - You ruined it.
-是我的错。-黄金，我告诉你。
- Yeah, my bad. - Gold, I tell you.
这里有黄金。
They got gold up in here.
幸运的。
Lucky.
挂紧。
Hang tight.
我马上就回来。
I'll be back.
我们走吧。
Let's go.
你卖了多少?
How many you sold?
有多少?
How many?
十个
Ten.
你卖了老爷子的十匹马?
You sold ten of Pops' horses?
我要把他们找回来。
I'm gonna get 'em back.
-你能待在外面吗?——为什么?
- Can you stay out here? - Why?
我在发展一种商业关系
I'm developing a business relationship,
你现在是个累赘。
and you're a liability right now.
我怎么成了负债?
How am I a liability?
你怎么成了lia…
How are you a lia...
别在工作中推销你的狗屁东西。
Don't promote your fucking side shit on the job.
-我的天啊-演员，歌手，舞者，
- Oh, my God. - Actor, singer, dancer,
裁缝,摩托车。
seamstress, motorcycles.
你想推销什么，就推销这门生意。
You want to promote something, promote this business.
不,橙汁。不。
No, OJ. No.
首先，那不是我的附属品。这是。
First of all, that's not my side shit. This is.
其次，如果有人是个累赘…
And second of all, if anybody's a liability...
去你妈的。-不，去你的。
- Fuck you. - No, fuck you.
嗨。我是来自朱庇岛的安珀。
Hi there. It's Amber again from Jupe's Claim.
看起来我们确实能挤出来，
It does look like we were able to squeeze out, uh,
几张额外的媒体通行证
a couple of extra press passes
为即将到来的朋友和家人预览。
for the upcoming friends and family preview.
哦。没有必要道歉。
Oh. No apology necessary.
这是指最大最好的，
This is in reference to the biggest, bestest,
我们将在公园迎来全新的现场表演
brand-new live show we have coming up here at the park,
——它正在悄悄靠近我们……——进来。
- which is sneaking up on us... - Come in.
如果你愿意，我可以把你放下来…
If you'd like, I can go ahead and put you down...
橙汁。
OJ.
谢谢大家的到来。
Thanks for coming up.
你过得如何?这是我妹妹艾米。
How you doing? This is my sister Em.
嗨。
Hi there.
所以,嗯…你带谁来了?
So, uh... who'd you bring me?
呃,幸运。
Uh, Lucky.
他是我第二好的马，你知道的，呃…
He's my second-best horse, you know, uh...
他失去了焦点。
He lost focus.
所以,嗯…我也是，但我不能炒了自己。
So, uh... I mean, I did, too, but I can't fire myself.
——这很好。——举起。
- That's good. - Hold up.
这你吗?
This you?
你真的是《i> kid Sheriff》里的亚洲小孩吗?
You literally the Asian kid from Kid Sheriff?
-嗯嗯嗯…-不，没关系。
- Em, Em, Em, Em... - No, it's okay.
是的，我在…我是小朱普。
Yeah, I was, uh... I was Lil' Jupe.
老兄，你是我最喜欢的。
Ah, dude, you were literally my favorite.
你介意我拍张照片吗?
You mind if I get a picture real quick?
你介意我们谈谈吗?
Hey, you mind if we talk?
是的。当然。
Yes. Of course.
请浏览。
Please, browse away.
Su casa es mi casa.
谢谢你！我一定会的。
Thank you. I sure will.
嗯,所以…
Um, so...
相同的协议,是吗?Eleven-five吗?
same deal, yeah? Eleven-five?
-是的。谢谢你！——这是3 d。是的。
- Yeah. Thank you. - That's 3D. Yeah.
那个黑人男孩怎么样了?他很好。
Whatever happened to that Black boy? He was good.
停下来,停下来。
Stop, stop.
他很好。
He was good.
其实我想做些铺垫，
I actually wanted to, uh, lay some groundwork,
通往一条，把它们买回来的路。
uh, to a pathway of-of, uh, buying some of them back.
好吧?
All right?
-是的。——嗯。
- Yeah. - Mm-hmm.
是的。完全。
Yeah. Totally.
嗯…
Um...
-是的。——是吗?
- Yeah. - Yeah?
实际上,橙汁,
Actually, OJ,
我给你爸的条件还在。
the offer I made your dad is still on the table.
哦,嗯…
Oh, uh...
-让我…让……-等一下
- Let me... Let... - Yo, wait a minute.
所以,这……
So, that...
OJ，我给你看过这个吗?
OJ, have I shown you this?
这是关于 Gordy's Home事件。
This is in reference to the Gordy's Home incident.
戈迪的家。是的,是的。
Gordy's Home. Yeah, yeah.
所以， Gordy's Home是一个短暂但传说中的情景喜剧
So, Gordy's Home is a short-lived but fabled sitcom
我在96年《我>少年警长》《我>爆了》之后主演的。
I starred in in '96 after Kid Sheriff blew up.
我爸爸跟我说过这个节目。
Yeah, my pops told me about this show.
那只猴子疯了还是怎么的。
The-the monkey went crazy or some shit.
你知道，我通常会收钱的。
You know, I usually charge a fee for this.
哦,该死的。
Oh, damn.
哈哈。
Ta-da.
嗯。
Hmm.
这是第一次拳头碰撞爆炸。
That's the first exploding fist bump.
什么?真的吗?
What? Really?
是你们想出来的吗?
Y'all came up with that?
就像我说的，Gordy's Home开始播放
So, as I was saying, uh, Gordy's Home began airing
在96年的秋天…
in the fall of '96...
它一出就大受欢迎。
and it was an immediate hit.
收视率很高。
Uh, ratings were huge.
很好的评论。
Pretty good reviews.
真的很受欢迎。
Just really took off.
是的。
Yeah.
然后，有一天…
Then, uh, one day...
我们在拍一集
we were shooting an episode
第二季的名字叫《戈迪的生日》
in season two entitled, uh, "Gordy's Birthday."
,嗯…繁荣。
And, um... boom.
其中一只扮演戈迪的黑猩猩…
One of the chimps that plays Gordy just...
刚刚达到了他的极限。
just hit his limit.
这场浩劫持续了6分13秒。
And it was six minutes and 13 seconds of havoc.
电视网试图掩盖爆款，但它是一个奇观。
Network tried to bury hit, but it was a spectacle.
人们只是痴迷于此。
People are just obsessed.
你别拿我开玩笑了。
You're kidding me.
OJ，你说你听说了?
OJ, you said you heard about that?
嗯哼。所以他们才不让你用黑猩猩。
Mm-hmm. That's why they don't let you use chimps.
这是部分原因。
That's part of the reason.
现在《Gordy’s Home》的粉丝越来越多。
There's a growing Gordy's Home fan base out there now.
这对荷兰夫妇给了我5万
This Dutch couple paid me 50K
到这里来过夜。
to come in here and spend the night.
我没有问过。
I didn't ask.
这太疯狂了。
That's crazy.
那么，到底发生了什么，伙计?
So, what happened really, man?
你没看过 SNL的坏戈迪小品吗?
You haven't seen the Bad Gordy sketch on SNL?
我是说，他们做得比我好。
I mean, they pretty much nailed it better than I could.
-嗯-不是吗
- Mm. - No?
周六夜现场吗?
Saturday Night Live?
达雷尔·哈蒙德饰演汤姆。
Darrell Hammond as Tom.
安娜·加斯泰尔饰演菲利斯。
Ana Gasteyer as Phyllis.
Cheri Oteri饰演Mary Jo Elliot。
Cheri Oteri as Mary Jo Elliot.
斯科特·沃尔夫是主持人。他的我。
Scott Wolf is the host. He's me.
当然，是小品的主角
But, of course, the star of the sketch
是克里斯·卡坦扮演的戈迪
is Chris goddamn Kattan as Gordy,
他是……
and he is...
不可否认的,好吗?
undeniable, okay?
是这样的。
Bit goes like this.
大家都想庆祝戈迪的生日，
Everyone's trying to celebrate Gordy's birthday,
但每次戈迪听到丛林的消息
but every time Gordy hears something about the jungle,
戈迪……Kattan……离开。
Gordy... Kattan... goes off.
这是……Kattan。
And it's... it's Kattan.
他简直太棒了。
He's just crushing it.
他是大自然的力量。
He is a force of nature.
他在舞台上表现出色。
He is killing on that stage.
是的。
Yeah.
这是传奇。
It's legendary.
传奇的大便。
Legendary shit.
是的。
Yeah.
是啊，我得先走了，
Yeah, I'm gonna have to go ahead,
去YouTube上看看吧。
look that one up on YouTube.
细节,你知道吗?
Details, you know?
完全。
Totally.
我还有工作要做。
I got some work I got to do.
那我们今晚就不能放松一下吗?
So we ain't gonna chill tonight, nothing?
-你想工作?——没有地狱。
- You want to work? - Hell no.
那你的条件是什么?
So, uh, what was the offer?
——女裙?-是的。
- Jupe? - Yeah.
他提出要买那座农场。
He offered to buy the ranch.
哦,真的吗?
Oh, really?
这很有趣。多少钱?
That's interesting. How much?
为什么?
Why?
因为……我想看看你到底有多蠢。
'Cause... I'm trying to see how big of a dumb-ass you are.
大笨蛋,也许。
Big dumb-ass, probably.
所以我猜你不想看到什么是好的
So I guess you don't want to see what's good
和爸爸的酒柜在一起，是吗
with Dad liquor cabinet, then, huh?!
其实我也买了大麻。
I got that hobby weed, too, actually.
那你就只能说这些了。
That's all you had to say, then.
爱好杂草。
The hobby weed.
你就说这么多，告诉我就行了。
That's all you had to say, just let me know.
你最开始就该把它扔了。
You should've dropped that at the top.
“我买了大麻。”你知道我准备好了。
"I got the hobby weed." You know I'm ready.
♪如果你看见我走在街上♪
♪ If you see me walking down the street ♪
♪每次见面我都开始哭泣…♪
♪ And I start to cry each time we meet... ♪
好吧，你的反应还是很快的。哇。
Okay, your reflexes are still quick. Like, whoa.
-我不生气。——我在看。
- I ain't mad at it. - I'm watching.
-♬走过去♬- EMERALD:对男人。
- ♪ Walk on by ♪ - EMERALD: To the man.
♪假装相信♪
♪ Make believe ♪
饮料。
Drink.
♪那你看不见的眼泪♪
♪ That you don't see the tears ♪
♪就让我一个人悲伤吧…♪
♪ Just let me grieve in private... ♪
哦,狗屎。
Oh, shit.
还记得牛仔外套吗?
Remember Jean Jacket?
是的,好马。
Yeah, good horse.
实际上，这应该是我的第一匹马。
Supposed to be my first horse, actually.
我刚和我的心理医生谈过这件事
I was just talking to my therapist about this
——就在不久前。——治疗师?
- not too long ago. - Therapist?
是的。我偶尔也上过一个。
Yes. I fuck one on occasion sometimes.
♪走过…♪
♪ Walk on by... ♪
我告诉她，在我九岁生日的时候，
I was telling her that, for my ninth birthday,
我本该去训练牛仔夹克的。
I was supposed to get to train Jean Jacket.
但老爷子买了些西部片，然后…
But then Pops got some Western, and...
牛仔夹克不再是我的了。
Jean Jacket wasn't mine no more.
典型的奥的斯高级。
Classic Otis Senior.
我清楚地记得……
I distinctly remember...
就站在这窗前
standing right here at this window,
看着你们训练我的马。
watching y'all train my horse.
我的马。
My horse.
老爷子从来没有抬头看我一眼。
Pops never looked up at me.
哇,现在。
Whoa, now.
哇,现在。哇,现在。
Whoa, now. Whoa, now.
橙汁,来吧。
OJ, come on.
但你做到了，黑鬼。
But you did, nigga.
还记得吗?
Remember?
Scorpion King，。
It was Scorpion King, actually.
它不是一部西部片。
It wasn't a Western.
那是老爷子给我的第一份工作。
That was the first job Pops took me on.
没什么好玩的。
Wasn't much fun.
最后还是用了骆驼，所以…
Ended up using camels anyways, so...
重点是……
The point is...
是啊，去他妈的重点。
Yeah, fuck the point.
那人真他妈固执。
Yo, that man was hardheaded as fuck.
你也是。
And so are you.
就是这样。
That's it.
但在一天结束的时候，你必须……
But at the end of the day, you got to...
你得承认，老爷子…
you got to admit, man, Pops...
老爷子建造这个地方的时候做了些什么。
Pops did something when he made this place.
他改变了整个行业。
He changed the industry.
这是真实的。
That's real.
我不能就这么算了。
I can't just let that go.
白灵为什么会在竞技场?
Why is Ghost in the arena?
好是什么?
What's good?
是的。
Yeah.
嘿，嘿，艾米，艾米!
Hey, yo, Em. Em!
把它放下!
Turn it down!
好吧!
All right!
♬你们这代人相信谈话♬
♪ Your generation believed in talk ♪
♬我害怕走在……♪
♪ Scared of the very steps in which... ♪
嘿!
Hey!
他要去哪里?
Where he going?
如果我……
What if I...
如果我告诉你…
What if I told you...
你离开这里会不一样吗?
you'll leave here different?
过去六个月的每周五…
See, every Friday for the last six months...
我和我的家人做了见证
my family and I bore witness
一个绝对
to an absolute
场面。
spectacle.
嗯?
Huh?
你看到了吗?的力量?
You see it? The power?
鬼在哪里?
Where's Ghost?
-我不知道。——坚持。
- I don't know. - Hold on.
繁荣。停电了。
Boom. Power went out.
——看到了吗?——倒带。
- See? - Rewind.
停止。
Stop.
鬼说:“我不听。
Ghost talking about, "I ain't listening.
我不训练。我想做什么就做什么"
I'm not trained. I do whatever the fuck I want."
什么?
What?
你看到了什么?
What'd you see?
什么是糟糕的奇迹?
What's a bad miracle?
嗯?
Hmm?
他们有词来形容吗?
They got a word for that?
不。
Nope.
他们说是一架螺旋桨飞机之类的东西害死了老爷子。
They said it was a prop plane or something that killed Pops.
我从来没想过这事。
That shit ain't never made sense to me.
然后今晚，我听到白灵发出声音
Then tonight, I heard Ghost make a sound
我从没听过马叫。
I ain't never heard a horse make.
你看到了什么?嗯?
What did you see? Hmm?
它是大的。
It was big.
——有多大?——大。
- How big? - Big.
-它长什么样?-我不知道。
- What'd it look like? - I don't know.
这是太快了。
It was fast.
太快了。
Too fast.
太安静了，不可能是飞机。
Too quiet to be a plane.
橙汁。
OJ.
你说的和我想的一样吗?
Are you saying what I think you're saying?
我告诉你，我们不需要太多。
I'm telling you, man, we don't need a lot.
我们只需要足够的钱
We just need enough to make our shit
看起来和外面的不一样。
look different from what's out there.
你明白我的意思吗?喜欢……
You get what I'm saying? Like...
你知道我并不想让它跑起来。
You know I ain't trying to run it up.
我在网上查了一下，看到了很多乱七八糟的东西。
I just was looking online, and I seen a lot of shit.
你知道我破产了，对吧?
You know I'm broke, right?
我们用我的钱。
We'll use my money.
好了,闭嘴。看。
Okay, shut up. Look.
好吧。
All right.
在这里。5到100万。
There it is. Five to a hundred K.
-好吧，读一读。-你读过了，难语症患者。
- Well, read it. - You read it, dyslexic ass.
重点是像Cyber Dominion这样的网站
The point is a website like Cyber Dominion
会付5到10万
will pay five to a hundred K
寻找ufo的照片证据
for photographic evidence of UFOs and shit.
一百K ?
A hundred K?
这就是我第一次看到的。
And that's just what I saw on the first go.
现在我想起来了，去他的网络统治。
Now that I'm thinking about it, fuck Cyber Dominion.
这是一个时刻…我们的时刻。
This shit right here is a moment... our moment.
我们设置好它，用正确的方式释放它，
We set it up, release it the right way,
伙计，我说的是有钱和出名一辈子。
man, I'm talking rich and famous for life.
你过得如何?你看起来漂亮。
How you doing? You look pretty.
她看起来像有座大房子。
She look like she got a big house.
——如何?——如何?我们怎么扑灭它?
- How? - How what? How we put it out?
-嗯-我就是这个意思
- Mm. - Well, that's what I'm saying.
我们不只是为了赚快钱，好吗?
We don't just go for the quick cash-in, okay?
我们去最可信的平台做报道。
We-we go to the most credible platform to do the story.
——那是什么?就像奥普拉? -是的。
- What's that? Like Oprah? - Yeah.
比如 Oprah，。之后，每个人都想加入。
Like Oprah, for example. After that, everybody want in.
我是说有很多
Well, I'm saying there's plenty
网上的飞行视频。
of videos of flying shit online.
前几天我见过一个。 Oprah。
I saw one the other day. That wasn't on Oprah.
黑鬼，我可没说奥普拉。你说 Oprah.
Nigga, I didn't say Oprah. You said Oprah.
你爱我>
You love Oprah.
听着，我想说的是网上那些东西都是假的。
Look, all I'm saying is all that shit online is fake.
低质量。没人会得到我们想要的。
Low quality. Ain't nobody gonna get what we gonna get.
我们会得到什么?
What we gonna get?
——拍摄。拍摄什么?
- The shot. - What shot?
这张照片。的钱。
The shot. The money shot.
不可否认,奇异,…
Undeniable, singular, the...
-  Oprah shot。-  Oprah ?
- the Oprah shot. - The Oprah shot?
原谅我。
Excuse me.
你好。我可以帮你。
Hi. I can help you over here.
嗨。
Hi.
谢谢你在Fry's购物。-
Thank you for shopping at Fry's. -
你们今天找的东西都找到了吗?
Did you guys find everything you're looking for today?
是的……天使。
Yes... Angel.
哦。太好了。
Oh. Great.
事实上，你有我们的名片吗?
Um, actually, do you have a card with us?
不了,谢谢。
No, thank you.
你要来一杯吗?
Uh, would you like one?
——因为它……-不用了，谢谢。
- Because it... - No, thank you.
你需要我们的技术支持人员吗
Would you like one of our tech support personnel
帮你安装?
to help you with the installation?
不，不，不，谢谢。
No, no, no, no, no, thank you.
感谢你。
Appreciate you.
好吧，没人帮忙安装。
All right, uh, no help with the install.
随便你。
Suit yourself.
它是硬安装吗?
Is it a hard install?
对我来说，没有。
Well, for me, no.
你做不到的。
You're not gonna be able to do it.
发生了什么事?你们被抢了吗?
What happened? Did you guys get robbed?
嗯哼。是的,你知道的。
Mm-hmm. Yeah, you know.
经常停电。
A lot of blackouts.
时不时把相机拿出来。
Take the camera out from time to time.
所有这些新相机，都有备用电池，
All these new cameras, they have backup battery power,
所以你应该没事。
so you should be fine.
但停电也会影响电池的能量，
But the outages affect the power in the battery shit, too,
像手机一样。
like cell phones.
好的。好吧。
Okay. All right.
手机，它们不只是电量下降。对吧?
Cell phones, they don't just drop in power. Right?
我是说，也许你的无线网络中断了
I mean, maybe your Wi-Fi drops out
当你的系统下降时。
whenever your system dips.
所以,这就是技术。
So, that's technology.
好吧，也许你在UFO热点。
Okay, or maybe you're in a UFO hot spot.
没有人相信这一点。
No one believes in that.
有什么事吗?
What's up?
该死的。没想到你们已经走了这么远了。
Damn. Did not realize you guys were this far out.
嗯哼。
Mm-hmm.
不过我不介意。
I don't mind, though.
马粪味和新鲜空气。
Smell of horse shit and fresh air.
对吧?
Right?
哇,哇,哇,
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
哇,哇,哇。
whoa, whoa, whoa.
哇。看着我，伙计。
Whoa. Look at me, man.
——操。-别这样。不要喊。
- Fuck. - Don't do that. Don't yell.
对不起,男人。
Sorry, man.
抱歉，如果我今天早上有点心不在焉的话。
Sorry if I was, like, a little shut down this morning.
刚结束一段四年的感情。
Just got out of a four-year relationship.
你是很好。
You were fine.
我知道这听起来很他妈的cliché，好吧，
I know it's gonna sound fucking cliché, all right,
但我以为她就是我的真命天子?
but I thought that she was the one, you know?
这需要一个小时以上吗?
Is this gonna take longer than an hour?
这个吗?哦,狗屎,是的。
This? Oh, shit, yeah.
-我先出去了-你要去哪?
- I'm-a go ahead and pop out. - Where you going?
我得去商店买点东西。
I got to go to the store and get something.
别担心。你需要什么吗?
Don't worry about it. You need anything?
哟。
Yo.
她叫丽贝卡·迪亚兹。
Her name was, uh, Rebecca Diaz.
没错，留意她。
Yep, keep an eye out for her.
她是个演员，模特，你知道吗?
She's an actress, model, you know?
她预定了CW的试播集，所以…
She booked a pilot on The CW, so...
是啊，他妈的离开我了。
Yeah, fucking left me.
是的,他妈的连续波。
Yeah, fucking CW.
-关于这台相机…-实际上，它能旋转起来吗?
- So, thing about this camera... - Actually, can it swivel up?
嗯,是的。
Uh, yeah.
——繁荣。-更?
- Boom. - Little more?
更多。好的。
More. Okay.
是的。
Yeah.
毫米。
Mm.
嗯,是的。
Uh, yeah.
嗯哼。
Mm-hmm.
你知道他们不再叫ufo了吗?
Do you know they don't call 'em UFOs anymore?
现在他妈的是uap了。
It's fucking UAPs now.
他们为什么要改名字?
Why they got to change the name?
是的。
Yeah.
完全正确。
Exactly.
不,操。我来告诉你为什么
No, fuck it. I-I'll tell you why
他们改了名字，好吗?
they changed the name, all right?
因为他们不想让我们知道。
It-it's 'cause they want to keep us in the dark.
还记得他们解密的时候吗
Remember when they declassified
几年前那些UFO的镜头?
all that UFO footage a couple years ago?
是的。人们开始注意了。
Yeah. Well, people started paying attention.
所以他们把名字改成了UAPs。
So they changed the name to UAPs.
没人知道UAP是什么，
And no one knows what the fuck a UAP is,
所以所有人都失去了兴趣。
so everyone lost interest.
我看见……海军剪辑。
I saw that... that Navy clip.
虽然我看不清他们。
Couldn't really see 'em, though.
可能是更好的。
Could've been better.
这是确凿证据的劣质录像
It's shitty footage of exact proof
有外星文明存在
that there's an alien civilization
在宇宙中。
out there in the universe.
所以,那是谁?
So, who's that?
来吧,男人。那些长着大眼睛的小家伙。
Come on, man. The little guys with the big eyes.
-嗯-是的
- Mm. - Yeah.
有很多理论。
There's lots of theories.
要么他们是寻求和平的星际旅行者
Either they're intergalactic travelers looking for peace
或者未来派的人类会及时回来
or futuristic humans coming back in time
为了阻止我们毁灭地球，
to stop us from destroying the planet,
或者他们是世界杀手。
or they're fucking world killers.
行星驱逐舰。
Planetary destroyers.
也就是说他们一直在监视我们
And that means that they've been fucking watching us
研究我们，等待最佳时机把我们传送过来
and studying us, waiting for the perfect time to beam us up
然后把金属探针塞进我们的屁眼里。
and shove metal probes up our fucking asses.
酷。
Cool.
总之， Ancient Aliens， History Channel。
An-Anyway, Ancient Aliens, History Channel.
-小心点。——嘿!
- Watch that shit. - Hey!
嘿!
Hey!
来吧!帮个黑鬼!
Come on! Help a nigga out!
嘿。
Hey.
你知道在哪能找到几个壮硕的小伙子吗?
Know where I could find me a couple of big, strong fellas?
你好吗?
You good?
我很好。
I'm good.
——什么?——那是什么?
- What? - What's that?
哦,这个吗?
Oh, this?
就是训练我们订的马
You know, just, uh, training horses we ordered
我捡起来了。
that I picked up.
-你从哪儿弄来的?-别担心。
- Where'd you get it from? - Don't worry about it.
来吧，帮帮我。
Now, come on, help me out.
有你。
Got you.
好吧,所以…那是什么呢?
Okay, so... so what is that?
-是诱饵吗?-我告诉过你。
- Is it like bait? - I told you.
这是用来训练马匹的诱饵。
It is a decoy for horse training.
好的。
Okay.
大便。大便。
Shit. Shit.
——看到了吗?——橙汁。
- See? - OJ.
我们很好。我是说，他什么都不知道。
We good. I mean, he don't know shit.
哦,不。你们在做一些见不得人的事。
Oh, no. You guys are doing something shady.
嘿!
Hey there!
Hey!
不过，你可以呆在那里!
You can stay right there, though!
当然!
Sure!
有什么事吗?
What's up?
我们在设圈套!
We're setting up a decoy!
马训练!
For horse training!
哦,好!
Oh, good!
你知道，我们有一些!
You know, we got some of those!
你得到…
Where'd you get...
你从哪弄来的?!
Where'd you get yours?!
是的…我不太确定!
Yeah... I'm not really sure!
我妻子会知道的!
My wife would know!
——好吧!谢谢你过来!-为什么…嘘。
- Okay! Thanks for stopping by! - Why the... Shh.
你不住在这里。
You don't live here.
对不起。试图帮助。
Sorry. Trying to help.
确定的东西!
Sure thing!
嘿。我想邀请你参加我们的……
Hey. I wanted to invite you to our...
新家庭直播秀!
new family live show!
星期五!下午5点!
Friday! At 5:00 p.m.!
好吧!
Okay!
拇指u…竖起大拇指。
Thumbs u... thumbs up.
我应该这么做吗?
Should I do it?
是的,这样做。
Yeah, do it.
竖起大拇指!
Thumbs up!
路由器在小屋里。
And so, the router's in the shed.
我设置好了，如果摄像头A断电，
I set it up so if the power goes down on camera A,
摄像机B指向天空拍摄
camera B's pointed at the sky to catch
不管是什么东西把它取出来的。
whatever might have taken it out.
反之亦然，所以…
And, uh, vice versa, so...
谢谢你！
Thank you.
我是说，你真的不会告诉我的
I mean, you're really not gonna tell me
这他妈的是怎么回事?
what the fuck is going on?
-你很快就会知道的。——哦。
- You'll know soon enough. - Oh.
酷,神秘。
Cool, cryptic.
他妈的迪克斯。
Fucking dicks.
如果你想的话，我可以远程监控。
I can monitor the feeds remotely myself, if you want.
免费的。
Free of charge.
——没有地狱。——没有。
- Hell no. - No.
砰，砰，谢谢你，女士。
Wham, bam, thank you, ma'am.
一件事。
One more thing.
你会接到我上司的电话
You'll be getting a call from my supervisor
问我的服务怎么样。
asking how my service was.
五颗星,天使。五颗星。
Five stars, Angel. Five stars.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
-那现在怎么办?-我不知道。
- So, what now? - I don't know.
-你想做什么?——我……你想做什么都行。
- What you want to do? - I'm... Whatever you want to do.
我还有工作要做。
Well, I got some work I got to do.
我要出去……
I'm gonna go out...
这个很好。
That's a good one.
♬♬，划♬
♪ Fisherman, row ♪
♪继续划你的船吧♪
♪ Keep on rowing your boat ♪
♬我的兄弟，我的兄弟，对，行……♪
♪ Brother man, brother man, yeah, row... ♪
今天我要和那些说
I'm talking today to women who say
他们被另一个星球的外星人绑架了。
they have been abducted by aliens from another planet.
我可以简单地说，我不知道一个事实吗
May I briefly say, I don't know for a fact
他们来自另一个星球。
that they're from another planet.
你知道你不是
Well, you know you weren't
在堪萨斯，托托。
in Kansas anymore, Toto.
我也没穿红鞋
And I wasn't wearing red shoes
我也能合拍-是的,是的。
that I could click together, either. -Yeah, yeah.
♪住在竹屋里♪
♪ Living in a bamboo hut ♪
♬在一个古老的海港小镇
♪ In a little old seaport town ♪
♬地板上有三个孩子……♪
♪ Three kids on the floor... ♪
没有。毫米毫米。不,我出去了。
Nope. Mm-mm. Nope, I'm out.
我走了。他妈的这大便。
I'm going. Fuck this shit.
好的。好的。
Okay. Okay.
噢。
Ow.
——哦,狗屎!——滚蛋。
- Oh, shit! - Fuck off.
把我们的财产还给我们。
Give us back our property.
不要扰乱木星的声明!头里。
Don't mess with Jupiter's Claim! -Come on.
发生了什么事?
What happened?
公园里的孩子。
The Park kids.
上衣的儿子。
Jupe's sons.
他们把克拉弗放出来了。
And they let Clover out, man.
什么?他们想恶作剧海伍德?
What? They trying to prank Haywood?
——这是!-嗨。你偷了他们的马。
- It's on! - Hey. You stole their horse.
哦。
Oh.
是的。
Yeah.
-嗨。——大便。
- Hey. - Shit.
哦。
Oh.
怎么了,尼斯湖水怪?
What's up, Nessie?
并不多。只是袜子大便。
Not much. Just stocking shit.
你知道，很正常。
You know, pretty much regular.
哦,狗屎!
Oh, shit!
我要去睡觉了。
I need to take my ass to bed.
——谁呢?-我是弗莱餐厅的天使。
- Who this? - Yo, it's Angel from Fry's.
我只是想告诉你，a台摄像机有故障。
Just calling to tell you that there is a bug on camera A.
我知道。等等，我不是告诉过你不要看我们的东西吗。
I know. Wait, I thought I told you not to watch our shit.
是的，我知道，我知道。
Yeah, I know, I know.
B摄像机坏了。
Camera B is down.
什么?
What?
B摄像机坏了。
Camera B is down.
就像 Ancient-fucking-Aliens 。
Like Ancient-fucking-Aliens down.
——嘿!-嗨。嗨。
- Hey! - Hey. Hi.
祖母绿，你能把虫子从那上面弄下来吗?
Emerald, can you please get the bug off the thing?
把虫子从这该死的东西上弄下来!
Get the bug off the fucking thing!
大便。
Shit.
你看到了什么?
Um, what do you see?
你……你看到灯光之类的东西了吗?
Do you... do you see, like, lights or anything?
就像一个碟子?
Like, a-a fucking saucer?
它在云端。它在云端。
It's in the cloud. It's in the cloud.
橙汁!它在云端!
OJ! It's in the cloud!
嗯哼。
Mm-hmm.
是的，不，不，不。
Yeah, nah, nah, nah.
运行,橙汁!快跑!
Run, OJ! Run!
大便。
Shit.
喂?
Hello?
OJ怎么了?
What happened to OJ?
它很好。
It's fine.
来吧。
Come on.
好吧，它还开着。
Okay, it's still on.
摄像头还开着。
The camera, it's still on.
该死，该死，该死，该死，该死。
Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit.
好了，你这该死的螳螂。
Okay, you fucking praying mantis.
好吧,婊子。
All right, bitch.
你喜欢酸味软糖吗?
You like Sour Patch Kids?
嗯?
Huh?
一个'ight,的人。
A'ight, man.
你的屎在哪里?我们走吧。
Where your shit? Let's go.
好久没见过这种人了。
Haven't seen one of those in a minute.
他妈的螳螂。
Fucking praying mantis.
那个混蛋最好别让我看到他，
That motherfucker better pray I don't ever see him,
如果我说了，我就吃了他。
'cause if I do, I'm-a eat him.
——走吧。——在哪里?
- Let's go. - Where?
伙计，我不知道。
Man, I don't know.
我在阿特沃特出了点状况
I got me a little situation in Atwater
现在就回我短信。
texting me back right now.
-今晚不会再来了。-我不在乎。
- It's not coming again tonight. - I don't care.
不。不。
No. No.
不。
No.
兄弟，我从没见过这样的事。
Bro, I ain't never seen no shit like this.
不值得。
It ain't worth it.
不,不。它是太多了。
No, nope. It's too much.
那你该走了。
You should go, then.
反正我也得早起。
I got to get up early anyway.
我要养家糊口。
I got mouths to feed.
大便。
Shit.
他妈的,他妈的,他妈的!
Shit, shit, shit!
你听到了吗?
You hear that?
鬼。
Ghost out there.
所有的领土。
Acting all territorial.
毫米。
Mm.
我想有些动物是不适合训练的。
I guess some animals ain't fit to be trained.
——你好吗?——呃,嗨。
- Hello? - Uh, hi.
这里是鹿角庄园吗?
Is this, uh, Antlers Holst?
这是谁?
Who's this?
嘿,是的。我是翡翠海伍德。
Hey, yeah. I'm Emerald Haywood.
我们几天前在广告上见过。
Uh, we met a couple days ago at the commercial.
哦，是的，骑马的女孩。确定。
Oh, yeah, horse girl. Sure.
我记得你和你哥哥。
I remember you and your brother.
是的,马的男孩。
Yeah, horse boy.
他也在这里。
He's here, too.
-骑师的后代。-是的。
- The descendants of the jockey. - Yeah.
看来我要跟电影公司的皇室成员说话了。
Guess I'm talking to motion picture royalty, then.
你怎么知道号码的?
How'd you get the number?
-我从电话名单上查到的——啊。
- I got it from the call sheet. - Ah.
我们有个项目，
So, we have a project, and, uh,
如果我告诉你这是千载难逢的机会呢?
you know, what if I told you it was the offer of a lifetime?
是的，希望不是我的一生。
Yeah, hopefully not my lifetime.
这个很好。我跟你说实话。
That's a good one. Um, I'm-a be real with you.
我们没有很多钱先付给你…
We don't have a lot of money to pay you up front...
你知道，不像你以前那样…但是,呃…
You know, not like you're used to... but, uh...
是的。我倾向于为他们做一个，所以我也可以为自己做一个，
Yeah. I tend to do one for them so I can do one for me,
那么到底是什么呢?
so what is it?
- - - - - -现实。-哦,不。现实。
- Reality. - Oh, no. Reality.
纪录片。
Documentary.
——Doc-Documentary。-这样好多了。
- Doc-Documentary. - Oh, that's better.
那么，它是关于什么的呢?
So, again, what's it about?
是关于梦想的狗屁组成，宝贝。
It's about the shit dreams is made of, baby.
听着,马姑娘。
Listen, horse girl.
我有一个，呃…
I got a, uh...
烤箱里的柠檬挞超赞的
pretty damn superb lemon tart in the oven
我要为我的十个好朋友服务，所以…
I'm about to serve to ten of my closest friends, so...
停止。
Stop.
-停，停，停-等一下什么?
- Stop, stop, stop. - Oh, hold on one second. What?
-他不是为这个来的-听着，听着，不
- He's not here for that. - Look, look, no.
不要可爱。按照计划行事。说它!
Don't be cute. Stick to the plan. Say it!
这就是我的工作。我不去做你的工作
This is what I do. I don't go to your job
然后用你的手把马的鸡巴敲出来。
and knock a horse's dick out your damn hand.
——你好吗?-是的。
- Hello? - Yeah.
是的,我的坏。我们很好,男人。
Yeah, my bad. We good, man.
根据美国电影杂志，
Um, according to American Cinema magazine,
你把电影上的不可能变成可能。
you make the cinematically impossible possible.
我们要找的是不可能的镜头。
Well, we looking for the impossible shot.
这是不可能的。
That's impossible.
鹿角。
Antlers.
在阿瓜·达尔西有个东西，
There's something out here in Agua Dulce,
你可能是世界上唯一的一个人
and you're probably the only person in the world
这样就能拍到电影了。
that can get it on film.
Th-That。
Th-That's it.
马女，你追逐的梦想，
Horse girl, this dream you're chasing,
你最终到达山顶的那个，
the one where you end up at the top of the mountain,
所有的目光都在你身上……
all eyes on you...
这是一个你永远不会醒来的梦。
it's the dream you never wake up from.
我不喜欢他。
I don't like him.
天呐这是真实的。
Holy shit. It's real.
我不知道你来干什么，但是…
I don't know what you're doing here, but...
你这样做是违法的。
it was illegal for you to...
像那样监视我们。
spy on us like that.
等一下,你…你不知道?
Wait, you... you don't know?
好吧，你看到了就告诉我。
Okay, uh, tell me when you see it.
在那里。
There.
——不会移动。——没错。
- Doesn't move. - Exactly.
好吧，看看这个。
Well, look at that.
是的。是的,是的,好的。
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, okay.
我重新看了一遍录像，
I went back and scrubbed through the footage,
那片云一直在那里
and that cloud has been right there
至少在我设置好摄像头之后。
at least since I set the cameras up.
是啊，既然你提到了
Yeah, now you mention it,
我可能一直在看同一朵云
I've probably been looking at the same damn cloud
过去六个月的每一天。
every day for the last six months.
大便。
Shit.
所以，我的意思是，他们在那里。
So, I mean, that's them in there.
我们一直在录，所以我们拿到了。
And we've been recording it, so we got it.
对吧?
Right?
是的。
Yeah.
你为什么这么说"是" ?
Why you saying "yeah" like that?
我是说，我们有外星人存在的视频证据。我…
I mean, we have proof of aliens on video. I...
是的，我不认为这是证据。
Yeah, I wouldn't call it proof.
你是认真的吗?
Are you serious?
我以前在网上看到过疯狂的天气现象。
Look, I've seen crazy weather phenomenons online before.
-我就是这个意思。——他是对的。
- That's all I'm saying. - He's right.
很好，但不是这样。不是奥普拉。
It's good, but it ain't it. Ain't Oprah.
不是奥普拉。
Ain't Oprah.
好的。是你们告诉我的吗
Okay. Are you guys telling me
有一艘外星飞船
that there's an alien spaceship
就在那该死的云里?
in that fucking cloud right there?
它不像船一样移动。
It doesn't move like a ship.
你什么意思，OJ?
What you mean, OJ?
如果不是船呢?
What if it's not a ship?
好了，Gordy，我们快准备好了
All right, Gordy, we're almost ready, buddy.
来吧，伙计。来吧。
Here we go, buddy. Come on.
——他是准备好了。——设置。
- He's ready. - Set.
我们开始吧。
Here we go.
和…行动。
And... action.
当然，我把它设成了冰岛时间
And, of course, I set it to Icelandic time
因为我们都热爱北极光，戈迪。
because we share a love of the aurora borealis, Gordy.
你根本不知道怎么看时间。
And you have no idea how to tell time.
伟大的礼物,爸爸。
Great gift, Dad.
把事情想清楚的方法。
Way to think things through.
不知为何，你会认为一个能派
Somehow, you'd think that a man who can send
火箭进入太空就能做到这一点
a rocket into space would be able to manage
一份像样的生日礼物。
a halfway decent birthday present.
不。
Nope.
你知道，戈迪，综合考虑，
You know, Gordy, all things considered,
也许我的天赋也没那么差。
maybe my gift isn't so bad after all.
——哦。——哦。
- Aw. - Aw.
嘿,戈迪。
Hey, Gordy.
——惊喜!——哇。
- Surprise! - Wow.
这是一种礼物。
Now, that is a gift.
哦。对不起。我的…
Oh. Sorry. My...
没关系。从那里开始吧。
That's all right. Pick it up from there.
等一下。
Wait a minute.
我们不是都找不到好礼物吗?
What happened to we both failed at finding good presents?
给你，戈迪。生日快乐。
Here you go, Gordy. Happy birthday.
哦,美丽,海莉。
Oh, beautiful, Hayley.
哇，嘿，嘿，嘿。没有。
Whoa, hey, hey, hey. No.
——不,不!下来!下来!戈迪!——下!
- No, no! Down! Down! Gordy! - Down!
——没有。停!——不要!
- No. Stop! - Stop that!
哦,不。不，不，不。
Oh, no. No, no, no, no.
不，不，不。不,戈迪,不!不!
No, no, no, no, no. No, Gordy, no! No!
D-D-Down !下来!下来!
D-D-Down! Down! Down!
你坐!下来。
You sit! Down.
不,不,不。
No, no, no.
不,不,不!
No, no, no!
不,戈迪!
No, Gordy!
停!啊!
Stop! Ah!
不!不!
No! No!
7个刚刚在现场…哦,我的上帝。
Seven just on scene... Oh, my God.
感觉好吗?
Feeling good?
是的。
Yeah.
感觉良好。
Feeling good.
好。
Good.
好了。
There we go.
运行它。再播放一次，宝贝。
Run it. Run it one more time, babe.
好的。
Okay.
如果我告诉你…
What if I told you...
哟。这是,呃…暴风雨要来了。
Yo. It's, uh... Storm's coming.
只是擦了一下，安全起见。
Just tarping up, just to be safe.
嘿，你去哪儿?
Hey, where you going?
我是幸运的。
I'm-a get Lucky.
现在，我们不会让</i
Now, we're not gonna let
今天有几朵云就没意思了，是吧，伙计们?
a few clouds kill our fun today, are we, folks?
闲话少说，
So, without further ado,
欢迎来到木星星际套索体验!
welcome to the Jupiter's Claim Star Lasso Experience!
大家今天感觉怎么样?
How's everyone feeling today?
好吧。
All right.
今天天气真不错。
It's quite a doozy today.
我想感谢你们来到这里。
Uh, I want to thank you guys for coming out here.
但首先，再来一轮掌声
But first, how about another round of applause
为我的琥珀吗?
for my Amber?
我告诉你，那个女人是
I'll tell you, that woman is
能忍受我的疯狂真是个圣人。
a saint for putting up with all my craziness.
也敬那些蠢蛋们。
And to the knuckleheads up there.
的员工。上榜。
The staff. Shout-out.
好吧，好吧。
All right, all right.
这就够了。
That's enough.
我还想特别感谢
I also want to give a special thanks to
我的一个老搭档，我的初恋，
an old costar of mine and my first crush,
玛丽·乔·艾略特，各位!
Mary Jo Elliott, everyone!
是的。
Yeah.
好吧。
All right.
你准备好了吗?
You ready?
哦,来吧。这不是什么。
Oh, come on. That ain't nothing.
你准备好了吗? !
Are you ready?!
我们开始吧。
Here we go.
你选择。
You're chosen.
如果我告诉你…
What if I told you...
大约一小时后…
that in about an hour...
你离开这里会不一样吗?
you'll leave here different?
过去六个月的每周五，
See, every Friday for the last six months,
我和我的家人都作证了
my family and I have bore witness
非常壮观。
to an absolute spectacle.
你们今天就会在这里看到。
One that you'll be seeing here today.
让我带你回到第一晚。
So let me take you back to that first night.
就在这个地方
Right here in this exact spot,
我会过来和一匹栗色的叫扳机的马争论。
I'd come over to wrangle a chestnut horse named Trigger.
现在，我几乎看不到我的手在我的面前
Now, I could barely see my hand in front of my face
因为雾，但我发誓
for the fog, but I swear
以我妻子和孩子的性命起誓
on my wife and children's lives
下午6点13分，
that at 6:13 p.m.,
我明白了…
I see...
一个飞碟
a flying saucer
在薄雾中下降。
descend through the mist.
"老扳机"直接冲进了峡谷。
Old Trigger took off straight into the gulch.
,嗯…
And, well...
就像他要回家一样。
it's like he was going home.
先说清楚，我们看到的
Now, just to be clear, what we saw
是一个飞碟。
was a flying saucer.
这是毫无疑问的。
No doubt about that.
前面稍微平一点，
Slightly flatter in the front,
底部有个圆孔
with a circular hole in the bottom
大约是两辆校车的长度。
about two school bus lengths wide.
女士们先生们，我不骗你们。
Ladies and gentlemen, I kid you not.
我们被监视了
We are being surveilled
一个被我称为"观察者"的外星物种
by an alien species I call "the Viewers."
虽然他们还没有从船上出来，
And though they have yet to emerge from their ship,
我相信他们信任我。
I believe they trust me.
如果他们没有，我觉得我们都不会
If they didn't, I don't think any of us
现在就在这里。
would be here right now.
就像我说的，不到一个小时，
So, as I said, in just under an hour,
星套索体验会改变你的。
Star Lasso Experience is gonna change you.
但首先，我的孩子们要出来
But first, my boys are gonna come out
为我们做点事。可以吗?
and do a little number for us. Would that be all right?
喧嚣。走,走,走……
Hustle. Go, go, go...
好的。我的小卫星:
All right. My little satellites:
科尔顿,凤凰城,马克斯。
Colton, Phoenix, Max.
记住这些名字，伙计们。
Remember those names, folks.
好了，开始!
All right, here we go!
那是什么?
What is that?
你们看到了吗?
Do you guys see that?
待在你们的座位上。
Uh, uh, stay in your seats.
这是新的。
This is new.
呃,他们早。
Uh, they're early.
他们今天要给我们来场真正的表演。
They're giving us a real show today.
-是的。-是的。
- That they are. - Yeah.
他们今天要给我们来场真正的表演。
They're giving us a real show today.
他们准备好了，我们也准备好了。
They're ready, we're ready.
欢迎来到星际套索体验，
Welcome to the Star Lasso Experience,
只有在朱庇特岛。
only at Jupiter's Claim.
-请记得避免…- - - - - -来吧。
- Please remember to avoid... - Come on.
用你的手机或任何闪光灯拍照…
Using your cell phones or any flash photography...
-大家把手机关掉。-在活动期间。
- Cell phones off, y'all. - during the event.
来吧!
Come on!
现在请忍耐一下。
Bear with us now.
训练过的动物可能是不可预测的。
Trained animals can be unpredictable.
现在坐好，坐在座位上享受吧
Now sit back, stay in your seats and enjoy
Star Lasso Experien…
the Star Lasso Experien...
牛仔和女牛仔，
Well, cowboys and cowgirls,
是时候在夕阳下启程了。
it's time to ride off into the sunset.
这是正确的。幸福的轨迹。
That's right. Happy trails.
它的关闭时间。
It's closing time.
你可以不回家，但你不能留在这里。
You don't have to go home, but you can't stay here.
再回来。
Come back again.
在那之前，我们祝你一切顺利。
And until then, we wish you well.
后会有期。再见。
Hasta la vista. Adios.
牛仔和女牛仔，
Well, cowboys and cowgirls,
是时候在夕阳下启程了。
it's time to ride off into the sunset.
这是正确的。幸福的轨迹。
That's right. Happy trails.
它的关闭时间。
It's closing time.
你可以不回家，但你不能留在这里。
You don't have to go home, but you can't stay here.
再回来。
Come back again.
和在那之前……
And until then...
幸运的。
Lucky.
Lucky，加油，加油。来吧!
Lucky, come on, come on. Come on!
快，快，快。
Come on, come on, come on.
幸运的。
Lucky.
快，快，快，快，快，快。
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
哟。
Yo.
这是完成了。
It's done.
好吧，我明早过来把那玩意扯下来。
All right, I'll be over in the morning to tear that shit off.
或者你们也可以自己动手。
Or you guys can do it yourselves.
-都一样。——不,不。
- It's all the same. - No, no.
-我喜欢你这么做。-你当然知道。
- I like when you do it. - Of course you do.
好的。明天见。
All right. See you tomorrow.
见到你。
See you.
接电话，接电话，接电话
Pick up, pick up, pick up,
接，接，接，接。
pick up, pick up, pick up, pick up.
加油！加油接电话，接电话，接电话。
Come on, come on. Pick up, pick up, pick up.
你知道吗?
Did you know that
这是第一批照片
the very first assembly of photographs
以连续的顺序制作一部电影
in sequential order to make a motion picture
是一个黑人骑马的两秒钟片段吗?
was a two-second clip of a Black man on a horse?
那人是巴哈马的骑师
That man was a Bahamian jockey
他就是阿利斯泰尔·e·海伍德
known as Alistair E. Haywood,
他是我的曾曾祖父。
and he was my great-great-grandfather.
-嗨。- Em。
- Hey. - Em.
我是对的。
I was right.
它不是船。
It's not a ship.
发生了什么事?
What happened?
♬我晚上戴墨镜
♪ I wear my sunglasses at night ♪
♬我可以，所以……♪
♪ So I can, so... ♪
他妈的什么?
What the fuck?
大便。
Shit.
它吃了他们，艾米。
It ate them, Em.
它把它们都吃掉了。
It ate them all.
它是活的艾米它是动物
It's alive, Em. It's an animal.
它有领地意识，会思考
It's territorial, and it thinks
这就是它的家。
that this is its home.
他们!
Em!
哦,他妈的。
Oh, fuck.
哦,狗屎。
Oh, shit.
哦,是的。
Ooh, yes.
嘿,嘿。我们有麻烦了。
Hey, hey. We're in trouble.
好吗?
Okay?
哦,他妈的。
Oh, fuck.
大便。
Shit.
什么?
What?
他妈的什么?
What the fuck?
那是谁?
Who the hell is that?
——他们!那是谁?——操。
- Em! Who the hell is that? - Fuck.
它上面的我们。
It's above us.
啊,狗屎!
Ah, shit!
大便。
Shit.
哦,狗屎!他妈的什么?
Oh, shit! What the fuck?
哦,上帝。
Oh, God.
发生了很糟糕的事。
S-Something very bad is happening.
他妈的!
Fuck!
是的,我们是失败的。
Yeah, we're fucked.
不。
Nope.
♬我晚上戴墨镜
♪ I wear my sunglasses at night ♪
所以我可以…♪
♪ So I can... ♪
♬它切断了我的安全♬
♪ It cuts my security ♪
♬她有♬吗
♪ Has she got ♪
♬控制我?♪
♪ Control of me? ♪
♬我转向她说:♪
♪ I turn to her and say... ♪
Em。橙汁的到来。
Em. OJ's coming.
我们走吧。
Let's go.
我得离开这房子。
Got to get out this house.
I got to get out this house.
不,st-st-stop。我们就不能等吗?
No, st-st-stop. Can't we just wait, right?
你可以。-不，我不会一个人待在这里的。
You can. -No, I'm not gonna be here alone.
我得离开这该死的房子!-不。
I've got to get out this fucking house! -No.
我们还活着，因为我们留在了这里。
We're alive still because we stayed here.
♬我戴着墨镜……♪
♪ I wear my sunglasses... ♪
走吧!
Go!
- - - - - -来吧。来吧。——走吧!
- Come on. Come on. - Go!
快，快，快，快。
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
加油！加油
Come on, come on.
走了。
Go.
是的,她……她会成功的。
Yeah, she... she gonna make it.
——橙汁。-她会挺过来的
- OJ. - She gonna make it.
-嘿，小马。-嘿，别看他
- Oh, hey, horsie. - Hey, don't-don't look him
-眼睛，拜托。——视效!
- in the eyes, please. - VFX!
集中在这里。集中在这里。
Focus here. Focus here.
来吧。
Come on.
♪我戴着墨镜♪-翡翠:走!
- ♪ I wear my sunglasses ♪ - EMERALD: Go!
♬晚上♬
♪ At night ♪
♬我晚上戴墨镜
♪ I wear my sunglasses at night ♪
♪我向你哭泣，我……♪
♪ I cry to you, I... ♪
欢迎来到我的酒馆。
Welcome to my tavern.
我不知道你听说了没有，一只可怕的野兽正在。
I don't know if you've heard, but a terrible beast is about.
它一直在骚扰村民，
It's been harassing villagers,
破坏庄稼，吃掉牲畜。
ruining crops and eating their livestock.
许多追求荣耀的猎人试图打败它，
Many a glory-seeking hunter has attempted to defeat it,
也有很多人死去。
and just as many have perished.
当你在这里……当你在这里……
While you're here... While you're here...
既然你在这里，请四处看看。
While you're here, please look around.
我现在在加州的阿瓜达尔西，
I'm here in Agua Dulce, California,
以及那40名客人和员工的行踪
and the whereabouts of those 40 guests and employees
当地西部主题公园的历史遗迹仍然未知。
of a local Western theme park are still unknown.
警长办公室已经忙得不可开交了
The sheriff's office has had its hands full
试图确认失踪人员的身份。
trying to identify the unaccounted for.
在那之前，只有一件事是确定的。
Until they do, only one thing is certain.
发生了一件奇怪的事情
There is something strange happening
在阿瓜达尔斯
out here in Agua Dulce.
当时监控录像是关闭的。
Security cameras were off at the time.
除此之外，我们没有理由怀疑是谋杀。
Other than that, we have, uh, no reason to suspect foul play.
我们确实有很多钱
We did have a considerable amount
雨水穿过这里，
of rain come through here,
所以我们不排除山洪暴发的可能
so we don't want to rule out flash flooding
可能起了作用。我们很明显…
as possibly having played a part. We're obviously...
炸鱼三明治永远不会出错。
You never go wrong with a fried fish sandwich.
鞑靼唐了。
Tartar got tang.
愚蠢的。
Stupid.
唐“鞑靼”?
"Tartar got tang"?
对吧?
Right?
我觉得如果你不看它的眼睛它就不会吃了你。
I don't think it eats you if you don't look it in the eye.
嘿,嘿!
Hey, hey!
RTR,兄弟。
RTR, bro.
你知道吗?
You know?
比如，解读房间。
Like, read the room.
没人想谈这个。
Nobody want to talk about that.
我们走吧!好的，好的，好的。足够了。
Let's go! -MAN 2: Okay, okay, okay. Enough.
好了，好了，好了，好了。
All right, all right, all right, all right, all right.
嘿,你幸运!
Hey, you lucky!
每个动物都有规则
Every animal got rules.
好吧?我们知道它想要什么，
All right? We know what it wants,
我们知道它是怎么来的，所以…
and we know how it comes, so...
他妈的。
Fuck.
我们什么都不知道。
We don't really know shit.
OJ，这是怎么回事?
OJ, what's this about, man?
这是什么呢?你想让我…
What's this about? You want me to...
你想让我说"对不起"吗?
You want me to say, "I'm sorry"?
“我错了”?“这是愚蠢的”?
"I was wrong"? "It's dumb"?
这不是愚蠢的。
It wasn't dumb.
-把握现在。——停止。
- Own the moment. - Stop.
-停下，停下。-很好。很好。
- Stop, stop this shit. - It was good. It was good.
但这一刻即将过去。
But the moment about to pass.
我们什么都不拥有。
And we don't own shit.
好的。我猜你们都住在我家吧。
Okay. Well, I assume y'all are crashing at mine.
对，因为你可以。
Right, 'cause you can.
因为我不会回去的
'Cause I'm not going back
敬那该死的大伞。
to the fucking monster umbrella.
得喂他们。
Got to feed 'em.
让幸运。
Let Lucky out.
有很多事情要做。
There's shit to do.
总是这样。
Always.
总有些事要做。
Always some shit to do.
你家屋顶上有个轮椅。
There's a wheelchair on your roof.
嗨。
Hi.
那片云一动都没动。
That cloud ain't moved a goddamn inch.
所以你不完全是胡说八道。
So you're not completely full of shit.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
是的。谢谢你！
Yeah. Thank you.
外星动物的概念
Th-The concept of extraterrestrial animals
在天空中飞翔并不是什么新鲜事。
in the sky is not a new thing.
你知道，人们一直在努力
You know, people been trying
从50年代就开始拍这些东西了。
to get pictures of these things since, like, the '50s.
-你知道，这是一个古老的…-我们怎么看?
- You know, it's an ancient... - How do we see it?
它又会饿的。
It's gonna get hungry again.
啊。
Ah.
所以,你知道…
So, you know...
只要按开饭铃就行了。
just ring the dinner bell.
现在我们知道它不喜欢什么了。
Now, we know what it doesn't like.
那个假马和假旗子把事情搞砸了。
That little fake horse and flags messed it up good.
卡在气管里了。
Got stuck in its windpipe or something.
我敢打赌，它一分钟内都搞不定这样的旗子。
I bet it ain't gonna fuck with flags like that in a minute.
是的。
Yeah.
我们把他惹毛了。
We pissed him off.
不是我们让它在这里定居的。
We're not the reason it settled down here.
那是胸衣。
That was Jupe.
他在试图驯服一个捕食者时被抓了。
He got caught up trying to tame a predator.
你不能这么做。
You can't do that.
你得和其中一个达成协议。
You got to enter an agreement with one.
是的。
Yeah.
问问齐格弗里德和罗伊吧。
Ask Siegfried and Roy.
好的。
Okay.
以一个在屋里的人的身份问
Um, asking as someone who was in the house
-出事的时候…毫米。
- when the shit went down... - Mm.
你要怎么跟一个他妈的…
How exactly do you enter an agreement with a fucking...
不明飞行物，外星实体，或者随便你叫它什么?
a UFO, alien entity or whatever the hell you want to call it?
牛仔外套。
Jean Jacket.
就叫他牛仔夹克吧。
Call him Jean Jacket.
那么，这个怎么样?
So, how about this?
我们把牛仔夹克寄给他怎么样
How about we send ol' Jean Jacket
黄金时间来几匹新鲜的马
some fresh horses in golden hour
看看会发生什么?-毫米毫米。
- and see what happens? - Mm-mm.
马的人。
Horse people.
为什么不放了他们呢?
Mm, why not just set them free?
我们不会那样做的。
We're not doing that.
好的。
Okay.
谁会去那里
Who is gonna go down there
然后把明星从他的拖车里弄出来?
and get the star out of his trailer?
我。
Me.
我会把他弄出来的。
I'll get him out.
你想把它放在哪里?
Where you want it?
你把他引出来。
You draw him out there.
我在这里。
I'm here.
在山脊上。
On this ridge.
哦,狗屎。
Oh, shit.
让她自己。
Made her myself.
没有电。
No electricity.
我不是告诉过你这混蛋要
Didn't I tell you this motherfucker was gonna
带着一台非电动相机上来吗?
come up here with a non-electrical camera?
我们走吧,孩子!
Let's go, boy!
是啊!
Yeah!
我已经在它下面待过几次了。
I've been up under it a couple times now.
我得到他。
I get him.
这是一种动物。
It's an animal.
你不能背对一只熊
You don't turn your back on a bear.
你不能在公牛周围穿红色的衣服
You don't wear red around a bull.
。
It's like that.
除非你想引起它的注意，否则你不会去看它
You don't look at it unless you want its attention.
晚安，斯托曼先生。
Good night, Mr. Storeman.
他妈的。我叫它礼帽。
Fuck it. I call top hat.
我们没有太多的时间了
And we ain't got a lot of time.
一天。两天,上衣。
One day. Two days, tops.
因为单词正在输出，当它输出的时候
'Cause the word is getting out, and when it does...
对不起,死人。公园的关闭。
Sorry, dead people. Park's closed.
你知道人们会来的
You know people gonna come
，然后像往常一样:
and do what they always do:
. . . .
try and take it all for themselves.
很好。
Fine.
顶针。
Thimble.
这就是我想要的。
That's the one I wanted anyway.
好吧，让他们来
Well, let 'em come.
这没关系，
It ain't gonna matter.
因为我们要做的是
'Cause what we about to do...
它们不能擦掉，
they can't erase that.
他很大，他很坏，
He's big, he's bad,
他很有精神。
and he's got a lot of spirit.
但任何有灵魂的东西都可能被破坏。
But anything with a spirit can get broke.
所以你打破了它。
So you break it.
我去打一针。
I'll get the shot.
嘿,嗯…
Hey, um...
我们正在做的事情很重要。
What we're doing's important.
对吧?
Right?
比如，我们所记录的，是…
Like, what we document, it's, uh...
会有好处的，对吧?
it's gonna do some good, huh?
我是说，除了金钱和名声，
I mean, besides the money and fucking fame,
比如，我们可以拯救一些生命。
like, we can save some lives.
靠，我们甚至可以拯救地球。
Fuck, we-we can even save Earth.
对吧?
Right?
-嗯-是的
- Mm. - Yeah.
♬嗯，它来到了地球
♪ Well, it came down to Earth ♪
♬它藏在一棵树里
♪ And it hid in a tree ♪
♬我说:“吃紫色的人♬先生。
♪ I said, "Mr. Purple People Eater ♪
♬不要吃我”
♪ Don't eat me" ♪
♬嗯，他看着我，用一种如此粗暴的声音♬
♪ Well, he looked at me and in a voice so gruff ♪
♬他说:“我不会吃你
♪ He said, "I wouldn't eat you ♪
♬因为你太坚强了
♪ 'Cause you're too tough" ♪
♬他是一只独眼，一只角
♪ He was a one-eyed, one-horned ♪
♬紫色的人吃♪
♪ Flyin' purple people eater ♪
♬是独眼♬，独角♬
♪ One-eyed, one-horned ♪
♬紫色的人吃♪
♪ Flyin' purple people eater ♪
♬是独眼♬，独角♬
♪ One-eyed, one-horned ♪
♬紫色的人吃♪
♪ Flyin' purple people eater ♪
当然看起来很奇怪，
Sure looks strange to me.
他不会惹你的。
He ain't gonna fuck with you.
是时候唤醒家人了。
Time to wake up the family.
我们开始吧。
Here we go.
出来吧，出来吧，不管你在哪里。
Come out, come out, wherever you are.
♪我被闪电击中♪
♪ I came down on a lightning bolt ♪
♬在我妈妈肚子里待了九个月
♪ Nine months in my mama's belly ♪
我出生的时候，接生婆尖叫着喊着
♪ When I was born, the midwife screamed and shout ♪
♬我嘴里冒着火焰和硫磺……♪
♪ I had fire and brimstone coming out of my mouth... ♪
这有多愚蠢啊?
How exquisitely stupid is that?
♬呐呐呐，呐呐呐
♪ Na-na-na, na-na-na ♪
♬呐呐，呐呐呐
♪ Na-na, na-na-na ♪
♬呐呐呐，呐呐呐
♪ Na-na-na, na-na-na ♪
♬呐呐，呐呐呐
♪ Na-na, na-na-na ♪
当我住在星空里的时候，我叫艾克苏马
♪ Exuma was my name when I lived in the stars ♪
♬艾克苏马曾经点亮过火星
♪ Exuma was a planet that once lit Mars ♪
♬我的喉咙里塞满了很多人的声音
♪ I got the voices of many in my throat ♪
♪青蛙的牙齿，山羊的尾巴
♪ The teeth of a frog and the tail of a goat ♪
♬我是Exuma♬
♪ I'm Exuma ♪
♬我是obeah人……♪
♪ I'm the obeah man... ♪
哈,哈,哈!
Hah, hah, hah!
♪Na-na-na Na-na-na…♪
♪ Na-na-na, na-na-na... ♪
我们今天会抓到你的，混蛋。
We gonna get you today, motherfucker.
-♬当我有我的♬-♬Obeah♬
- ♪ When I've got my ♪ - ♪ Obeah ♪
-♬我头上戴着大帽子♬-♬♬♬Obeah
- ♪ Big hat on my head ♪ - ♪ Obeah ♪
你知道我♬♬♬Obeah♬
- ♪ You know that I ♪ - ♪ Obeah ♪
♪♪能复活♪♪♪♪♪♪
- ♪ Can raise the dead ♪ - ♪ Obeah ♪
♬当我拿着拐杖的时候
♪ And when I got my stick in my hand ♪
♬你知道我是……♪
♪ You know that I am... ♪
霍尔斯特的摄像头在哪里?
Where is the feed for Holst's camera?
结束了。
Over.
想不出来。结束了。
Couldn't figure it out. Over.
你说不明白是什么意思?
What you mean, you couldn't figure it out?
结束了。
Over.
霍尔斯特在用胶片摄影机拍摄，
Um, Holst is shooting on a film camera,
我们所有的相机都是数码的，所以这是一个整体。
and all of our cameras are digital, so it's a whole thing.
结束了。
Over.
基本上，你忘记了。结束了。
Basically, you forgot about it. Over.
是啊，我忙得不可开交
Yeah, well, I had my hands full
把50个空中舞者绑在死人的汽车电池上
rigging 50 fucking sky dancers to dead people's car batteries
所有连接到一个控制面板。
all connected to one control panel.
所以，是的，他妈的结束了。对不起。
So, yeah, fucking over. Sorry.
我很害怕。
I'm scared.
人下来。
Man down.
人下来吗?什么?在哪里?
Man down? What? Where?
最后一个舞者，在峡谷深处。
Last dancer, deep in the gulch.
继续查，艾米，我熬夜了。
Stay on it, Em. I'm staying up.
草泥马。
Motherfucker.
哦,等等,等等。
Oh, wait, wait.
哦，它回来了。
Oh, it's back up.
可能是电池故障。
Could be a faulty battery.
好的。拍摄的。
All right. Shot's up, then.
不,他戳。
Nah, he's poking.
这个混蛋是谁?
Who's this asshole?
黑衣男人骑着白色摩托车。
Man in black on a white motorcycle.
不，不，不，不。大便。
No, no, no, no, no, no. Shit.
我能帮你吗?
Can I help you?
看到那朵云了吗?
You see that cloud?
嘿，伙计，你和谁在一起?
Hey, man, who you with?
哦,我很抱歉。
Oh, I'm sorry.
你是谁?
Who are you?
没有人。
Nobody.
在我看来你不像个无名小卒。
You don't look like a nobody to me.
听着，我们在做摄像测试
Yeah, look, w-we doing a camera test
为了Verizon的广告
for a Verizon commercial,
所以现在我需要你清理一下道路。
so now I'm-a need you to clear the road.
整个山谷看起来很模糊
This whole valley comes up as blurry
在谷歌地图上。
on Google Maps.
你还真是躲在这后面。
You're really tucked away back here.
木星的索赔?
Jupiter's Claim?
如果你反过来，会更快。
Quicker if you go the other way around.
是的。
Yeah.
实际上,
Actually,
朱佩·帕克和那些人到底怎么了?
what did happen with Jupe Park and all those people?
他基本上是你的邻居，对吧?
He was basically your neighbor, right?
所以呢，他们消失了?
So, what, they vanished?
你不相信洪水的故事，对吧?
You don't believe the flood narrative, do you?
他妈的,伙计们。
Fuck, guys.
这是我>
It's TMZ.
哦,操我。
Oh, fuck me.
哦,嘿,家伙。牛仔夹克绝对在云里，
Uh, hey, guys. Uh, Jean Jacket is definitely in those clouds,
他肯定是朝这边来了。
and he's definitely coming this way.
有什么事吗?你不想上电视吗?
What's the matter? Don't you want to be on TV?
伙计，我正想告诉你呢。
Man, I'm trying to tell you.
你不会想这么做的。
You don't want to go that way.
他妈的。
Fuck it.
你的损失,没有人。
Your loss, nobody.
我们仍然滚动吗?结束了。
We still rolling? Over.
没错。
Goddamn right we are.
伙计们，它来了。结束了。
Fellas, here it comes. Over.
突击测验,伙计们。
Pop quiz, guys.
电动自行车会发生什么
What happens when an electric bike
时速60英里撞上了反电场
going 60 miles per hour hits an anti-electric field
走反方向?
going in the opposite direction?
大便。
Shit.
他妈的。
Fuck.
大便。我们都会进监狱的。
Shit. We're all gonna go to jail.
哦,他妈的。那家伙不可能还活着。
Oh, fuck. There's no way that that guy's alive.
啊,狗屎。
Ah, shit.
该死的。
Goddamn.
我跟他说了别去。
I told his ass not to go.
我告诉他不要去。
I told him not to go.
嘿，OJ，怎么了…
Uh, hey, OJ, what's...
你他妈要去哪?
Wh-Where the fuck are you going?
他他妈在干嘛?
The fuck is he doing?
我要黑了。结束了。
I'm going dark. Over.
好的。不,橙汁,不。不!
Okay. No, OJ, no. No!
没有自尊的…
No self-respecting...
哇，哇，哇，哇，哇。
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
-嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿。-放松，放松，放松。-
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey. - Easy, easy, easy. -
你录下来了吗?
Did you get that on camera?
-看着我。看着我。-看着我。发生了什么?
- Look at me. Look at me. - Look at me. -What happened?
听着，听着，我们得把你弄出去。
Listen, listen, we-we got to get you out of here.
-看着我。-我的相机呢?
- Eyes on me. - Where's my camera?
——嘿!嘿!-我需要我的相机。
- Hey! Hey! - I need my camera.
你看到了吗?
Do you see it?
好的。天使吗?
Okay. Angel?
——什么?-安吉尔，别这样。
- What? - Angel, come on.
我们得重新装弹。
We got to reload.
大便。
Shit.
等等。
Wait.
你的手机呢?
Uh, where's your phone?
你为什么不拍下来?
Why aren't you filming this?
什么?
What?
天使,发生什么事情了?
Angel, what's happening?
好吧，OJ，如果你为了救那个人而死，
Okay, OJ, if you die trying to save that guy,
我要杀了你。
I'll kill you.
不。不,不,谢谢。
No. No, no, please.
请,不。不。-我们会救你出来的。闭上你的眼睛。
Please, no. No. -We're gonna get you out. Shut your eye.
-闭上眼睛。-先拍张照片再说。
- Shut your eye. - Not before you take a picture.
先照张相!
T-Take a picture first!
呃,相机重新加载。
Uh, camera reloads.
你可以用我的相机。
You can use my camera.
不,不。没有足够的时间。
No, no. There's not enough time.
这里的。
It's here.
蝎子王。
Be Scorpion King.
让自己出名。
Make a name for yourself.
那是什么?
What is that?
我的坏男人。嘿。
My bad, man. Hey.
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my God.
我的相机!我需要我的照相机!
My camera! I need my camera!
哦,我的上帝!他妈的!
Oh, my God! Fuck!
把盖子给我。把盖子给我。
Give me the lid. Give me the lid.
来吧。好吧。
Come on. All right.
哦,上帝!
Oh, God!
哦,他妈的!
Oh, fuck!
狗屎!他妈的!
Shit! Fuck!
嘿,嘿!大家都好吗?
Hey, hey! Is everybody okay?
看在上帝的份上，跟我说话，拜托!
For the love of fuck, talk to me, please!
橙汁。
OJ.
橙汁。橙汁!
OJ. OJ!
你这个混蛋，你最好回答我。
You stupid-ass motherfucker, you better answer me.
哇，哇，哇，哇
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
哇,哇,哇。
whoa, whoa, whoa.
你没事吧? !
Are you okay?!
你是好吗?结束了。
Are you good? Over.
哦,上帝!哦,上帝!
Oh, God! Oh, God!
哦,上帝!
Oh, God!
哦,上帝。
Oh, God.
哦,上帝!
Oh, God!
天啊，我想它要带走舞者了。
Holy shit, I-I think it's taking the dancers.
你听到了吗?
Are you getting this?
伙计们，OJ戴上兜帽了。
Guys, OJ's hooded up.
他在跑步。OJ要跑了!
He's doing the run. OJ's doing the run!
哦,上帝。
Oh, God.
嘿,这是一去不复返了。
Hey, it's gone.
我看不到了，伙计们。
I can't see it anymore, guys.
得到它。得到它!
Get it. Get it!
不。
No.
他妈的。
Fuck.
走吧!走吧!
Go! Go!
幸运,走了。走，走，走，走，走!
Lucky, go. Go, go, go, go, go!
神圣的狗屎!
Holy shit!
是啊!
Yeah!
我们走吧!
Let's go!
是啊，他不喜欢那样，对吧?
Yeah, he didn't like that, did he?
OJ，你他妈的真是个天才。
OJ, you're a motherfucking genius.
我们得到它。我们得到它。
We got it. We got it.
这是结束了。
It's over.
这是结束了。我们成功了，各位!
It's over. We got it, y'all!
信号开始进进出出的时候…
The feed started going in and out when...
当那个人被。
when that guy got got.
但我们应该被胶卷摄影机盖住。
But we should be covered with the film camera.
霍尔斯特?
Right, Holst?
光。
The light.
光,…
The light, it's...
很快就会变魔术了。
gonna be magic soon.
你是什么意思，蚂蚁?
What you mean, Ant?
哇,不,不。Wh-Where你要去哪里?
Whoa, no, no. Wh-Where you going?
会没事的，安吉尔。
It's gonna be all right, Angel.
我们不应该做不可能的事。
We don't deserve the impossible.
哦,嘿,家伙。
Uh, hey, guys.
霍尔斯特刚说了些诡异的鬼话。
Holst just said some creepy, cryptic shit.
带着他的相机。他向山上走去。
Took his camera. He's heading up the mountain.
结束了。
Over.
嘿,霍尔斯特。
Hey, Holst.
霍尔斯特。等待。等等,男人。
Holst. Wait. Hold on, man.
跟我说话。发生了什么事?
Talk to me. What happened?
你到底拍没拍?结束了。
Did you get the shot or didn't you? Over.
这个黑鬼。
This nigga.
他妈的。
Fuck.
这很疯狂，对吧?
This is crazy, right?
快，快，快。
Come on, come on, come on.
他妈的。
Fuck.
不,男人。
No, man.
他妈的?
The fuck?
霍尔斯特。
Holst.
哦,狗屎。
Oh, shit.
他妈的!
Fuck!
哦。
Oh.
哦,上帝。
Oh, God.
不。
No.
哦,狗屎。
Oh, shit.
他妈的。
Fuck.
什么?
What?
噢!
Ow!
他妈的。
Fuck.
好的。
Okay.
他妈的!
Fuck!
哦,狗屎!
Oh, shit!
哦,不!
Oh, no!
不要看。不要看。
Don't look. Don't look.
不要看。不要看。不要看。
Don't look. Don't look. Don't look.
不要看。不要看。
Don't look. Don't look.
不要看。不要看。不要看。
Don't look. Don't look. Don't look.
自行车!
Get the bike!
滚出去!
Get out of here!
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my God.
你死了!死了!
You're dead! Dead!
该死，该死，该死，该死。向下看。
Shit, shit, shit, shit. Look down.
嘿。
Hey.
哇。哇，哇，哇，哇。
Whoa. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
来吧。
Come on.
不。
No.
哦,他妈的。他妈的。他妈的。
Oh, fuck. Fuck. Fuck.
不!
No!
只是离开,橙汁。
Just leave, OJ.
忘记它!来吧!
Forget it! Come on!
来吧!
Come on!
它会毁了你的。
It's gonna fuck you up.
来吧。
Come on.
加油，加油!
Come on, come on!
什么……
What the...
来吧。来吧!
Come on. Come on!
我会抓到你的，混蛋。
I'm gonna get you, you motherfucker.
我要带你去奥普拉。我要带你去奥普拉。
I'm-a take you to Oprah. I'm-a take you to Oprah.
让我们看看奥普拉。
Let's go to Oprah.
是的!
Yes!
没人敢惹海伍德，贱人!
Nobody fucks with Haywood, bitch!
没有人!
Nobody!
你听到我吗? !
You hear me?!
牛仔和女牛仔,
Cowboys and cowgirls,
是时候在夕阳下启程了。
it's time to ride off into the sunset.
这是正确的。幸福的轨迹。
That's right. Happy trails.
它的关闭时间。
It's closing time.
你可以不回家，但你不能留在这里。
You don't have to go home, but you can't stay here.
再回来。
Come back again.
在那之前，我们祝你一切顺利。
Until then, we wish you well.
后会有期。再见。
Hasta la vista. Adios.
对，给她拍张照。放大。
Yeah, get a shot of her. Zoom in.
我们已经做好了准备。
We're ready.
我们准备好了，可以出发了。
We're set up, ready to go.
各位，这是沃利·帕琴科
Folks, this is Wally Pachenko
在阿瓜达尔斯现场报道
reporting live from Agua Dulce
就在朱庇特岛之外
just outside of Jupiter's Claim,
几秒钟前
where just seconds ago
一件无法解释的事情，就在不远处……
an inexplicable occurrence, uh, just in the distance...
你大概能听出我声音里的震惊。
You can probably hear th-the shock in my voice.
还有一些碎片，飘在空中
There are still some fragments, uh, floating in the air
哪里有不明物体
where some-some unidentified object
飘进了太空然后爆炸了。
just drifted off into space and exploded.
你可以看到一些碎片还在从天上掉下来。
Uh, you can see some fragments still falling from the sky.
我们会有一些很棒的…
Uh, we will have some amazing...